<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cluj Tour</string>
    <string name="food_tab">Food</string>
    <string name="aco_tab">Accommodation</string>
    <string name="atr_tab">Attractions</string>
    <string name="en_tab">Entertainment</string>

    <!-- Entertainment strings -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="park_name">Central Park Cluj</string>
    <string name="park_desc">Central Park is a large public, urban park in central Cluj-Napoca.
        It was founded in the 19th century and it located on the souther shore of Someşul Mic River.
        The Park is now home to the University of Arts and Design and to the Chemistry Faculty of the
        Babeş-Bolyai University.During 2012, the Central Park was site of an important restoration
        process, especially for the building of the Old Casino.</string>
    <string name="cetatuie_name">Panoramic Cetatuie</string>
    <string name="cetatuie_desc">The Cetatuie was built i between 1715 and 1735 with fences
        shaped like a star, having one tower and being surrounded by bastions. The place was build
        by the plan of the military architect Giovanni Murando Visconti.</string>
    <string name="imall_name">Iulius Mall Cluj</string>
    <string name="imall_desc">Iulius Mall Cluj is a shopping mall in Cluj-Napoca, Romania,
        and was opened on 10 November 2007. It has 205 stores and a 10 screens cinema complex, also
        food court. It's a really good place to spend free days.</string>
    <string name="pmall_name">VIVO Cluj</string>
    <string name="pmall_desc">Polus Center Cluj is a shopping mall located in Cluj-Napoca, Romania which opened on October 12, 2007.
        At the time of its completion it was the first shopping mall in Cluj-Napoca.
        It took 15 months to build Polus Center, and for nine months the construction site
        was also the biggest archaeological site in Romania. Among the finds was the tomb of a
        Gepid princess and a 3300-year-old tomb of a pair of lovers.</string>
    <string name="ipark_name">Iulius Mall Park</string>
    <string name="ipark_desc">This is an amazing place to be! The park
        is built around a lake making the warm summer days way better. Occasionally there are 
        organised music event.</string>
    <string name="bpark_name">Babes Park</string>
    <string name="bpark_desc">This park belongs to the University and it mostly serve as training
        environment for Sports Faculty's students. It has jogging routes, tennis terrain, swimming pools and gym.</string>
    <string name="dom_name">Royal Domain</string>
    <string name="dom_desc">Royal Domain is a complex close to Cluj-Napoca which offers
        multiple facilities such as swimming pool with both normal and termal water, spa and sauna.
        It also offers outside activities such as horse riding.</string>
    <string name="wonder_name">Wonderland Cluj</string>
    <string name="wonder_desc">Wonderland Cluj is mostly an even holder place, but you can also go there
        to spend free days relaxing at spa and swimming in amazing environment.</string>
    <string name="piata_name">Union Square Cluj</string>
    <string name="piata_desc">is the largest and most important squares in the Romanian
        city of Cluj-Napoca. The square is one of the largest in Romania, with dimensions
        of 220 m by 160 m. The central district of the city spreads out from this square.
        The St. Michael Church, with the highest church tower in Romania (80m), is the second
        largest Gothic-style church in Romania. The church was constructed in two phases.
        The first from 1316 to 1390 and the second from 1410 to 1487. Also, the statue of King of
        Hungary Matthias Corvinus is located here.</string>
    <!-- Food strings -->
    <string name="nobori_name">Nobori Japanese</string>
    <string name="nobori_desc">Address: Str. Plopilor 57&#8211;62 \nPhone: 0744 339 508 \nOpen: 11AM&#8211;11PM  </string>
    <string name="klausen_name">Klausen Burger</string>
    <string name="klausen_desc">Address: Str. Regele Ferdinand 22 \nPhone: 0372 717 552 \nOpen: 10AM&#8211;2AM</string>
    <string name="shanghai_name">Shanghai Cluj</string>
    <string name="shanghai_desc">Address: Str. Calea Turzii 42 \nPhone: 0264 442 027 \nOpen: 12PM&#8211;12AM</string>
    <string name="rex_name">Pizza Rex</string>
    <string name="rex_desc">Address: Str. Bolyai János 9 \nPhone: 0264 596 430 \nOpen: 11:30AM&#8211;11PM</string>
    <string name="viena_name">Bistro Viena</string>
    <string name="viena_desc">Address: Str. Matei Corvin 3 \nPhone: 0757 082 590 \nOpen: 12PM&#8211;1AM</string>
    <string name="livada_name">Livada Restaurant</string>
    <string name="livada_desc">Address: Str. Clinicilor 14 \nPhone: 0722 111 115 \nOpen: 11AM&#8211;12AM</string>
    <string name="aroma_name">Aroma Restaurant</string>
    <string name="aroma_desc">Address: Str. Calea Turzii 295 \nPhone: 0264 480 010 \nOpen: 11PM&#8211;11PM</string>
    <!-- Accommodation Strings -->
    <string name="belvedere_name">Hotel Belvedere</string>
    <string name="belvedere_desc">Address: Strada Călărașilor 1 \nPhone: 0264 432 071</string>
    <string name="napoca_name">Grand Hotel Napoca</string>
    <string name="napoca_desc">Address: Strada Octavian Goga 1 \nPhone: 0264 580 715</string>
    <string name="transi_name">Transilvania Hotel</string>
    <string name="transi_desc">Address: Strada Regele Ferdinand 20 \nPhone: 0264 594 429</string>
    <string name="melody_name">Hotel Melody Center</string>
    <string name="melody_desc">Address: Piața Unirii 29 \nPhone: 0264 597 465</string>
    <string name="paradis_name">Hotel Paradis</string>
    <string name="paradis_desc">Address: Strada Ciocârliei \nPhone: 0264 413 940</string>
    <string name="stil_name">Hotel Stil</string>
    <string name="stil_desc">Address: nr. 5B, Fagetului Street \nPhone: 0264 438 171</string>
    <string name="premier_name">Premier Hotel</string>
    <string name="premier_desc">Address: Strada Donath \nPhone: 0264 307 200</string>
    <!-- Attractions strings -->
    <string name="botanicm_name">Botanical Garden Museum</string>
    <string name="botanicm_desc"> The Botanical Institute accommodates the Botanical Museum,
        with a collection of about 7,000 items, grouped in the first part in the form of collections
        of scientific or economic importance, and in the second part, according to a phylogenetic criteria,
        in evolving order, beginning from plants with simple organization (algae, mosses, lichens, fungi),
        to plants with complex organization (gymnosperms and angiosperms).</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_name">Alexandru Borza Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_desc">The Botanical Garden covers 14 hectares, a varied land
        configuration suitable for the growth and development of plants from different continents.
        Around 10,000 specific categories are cultivated here, grouped for a better administration
        into several sectors: ornamental, phytogeographic, systematic, economic, greenhouses complex
        and the sector destined for persons with sight deficiencies - created recently in order to meet
        the needs expressed repeatedly by the community. </string>
    <string name="historynm_name">National Museum of Transylvanian History</string>
    <string name="historynm_desc">The National Museum of Transylvanian History (Romanian: Muzeul Național de Istorie a Transilvaniei) is a history and archaeology
        museum in the city of Cluj-Napoca, Romania. It features a permanent exhibition,
        as well as temporary exhibitions, the "Tezaur" exhibition, and Pharmacy Historical
        collection—this last opened in the Hintz House, an historical building in the city's center.</string>
    <string name="parc_etno_name">Ethnographic Park Romulus Vuia</string>
    <string name="parc_etno_desc">The museum has a collection of more than 50,000 objects reflecting
        the occupations, the habits and the life style of the Transylvanian rural population.
        Part of this collection is to be found in the Reduta Palace while the rest of the objects are
        in the open-air section. The most ancient objects here exhibited date from 1678.</string>
    <string name="forest_name">Hoia Forest</string>
    <string name="forest_desc">The Hoia-Baciu Forest ( World’s Most Haunted Forest ) is situated near
        Cluj-Napoca, Romania covers an area of ​​over 250 hectares and is often referred to as the
        Bermuda Triangle of the country. Hoia Baciu Forest ( World’s Most Haunted Forest ), has a
        reputation for intense paranormal activity and unexplained events. Reports have included, ghost
        sightings, unexplained apparitions, faces appearing in photographs that were not visible with
        the naked eye, and in the 1970s, UFO sightings were reported.</string>
    <string name="museums_name">Museum Square Cluj</string>
    <string name="museums_desc">The Museum Square, located in the heart of Cluj Napoca is
        one of the oldest markets in the city. It is named after Transilavnie History Museum
        that is in its end. The Old City Square, over time wore several names.
        Small Square was known in the Middle Ages (zhe Big Square was that surrouns
        St. Michael Church), and Karolina Square in the eighteenth and nineteenth centuries.
        Today is known as The Museum Square.</string>
    <string name="salina_name">Turda Salt Mine</string>
    <string name="salina_desc">Salina Turda is a salt mine located in the Durgău-Valea Sărată
        area of Turda, the second largest city in Cluj County, Romania. Salt was first extracted here
        during the antiquity and the mine continuously produced table salt from the Middle Ages
        (the mine being first mentioned in 1075) to the early 20th century (1932). The first document
        that speaks explicitly about the existence of a salt mine in Turda dates from 1 May 1271,
        being issued by the Hungarian chancellery. </string>
    <string name="farma_name">Pharmaceutical Museum Cluj</string>
    <string name="farma_desc">The Pharmacy History Collection can be found in the oldest pharmacy
        building of Cluj-Napoca, named “La Sfântul Gheorghe”, also known as the Hintz pharmacy,
        dating back to 1573.</string>
</resources>
